A Guide to the Old Dominion Postcard Club Records, 1979-2017
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Old Dominion Postcard Club Records, 1979-2017
The Library of Virginia
52556
1.8 cu. ft (4 boxes)
The Old Dominion Postcard Club
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Tom Ray.
Biographical Information
The Old Dominion Postcard Club was formed in April 1978 to bring together postcard collectors, the club has made it its mission to promote the collecting of postcards to civic groups, historical societies, and interested individuals.
Scope and Content
Records, 1979-2017, of the Old Dominion Postcard Club are primarily comprised of the club's newsletters, called the Virginian Deitologist. Newsletters include information about club members, club meetings and events, and interesting stories about postcards. Also included in the newsletters are articles about the history and symbolism of postcards, as well as local and national newspaper articles regarding postcards and postcard collecting. This collection also includes membership directories, the club's consitution and by-laws, rules regarding the club's annual postcard exhibit, fliers, correspondence, and general papers. In addition, this collection also contains several years of newsletters from the the affiliated Northern Virginia Postcard Club.
Contents List
- Newsletters, 1979, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Newsletters, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Newsletters, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Newsletters, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Newsletters, 1991-1992 and undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Newsletters, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Newsletters, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Newsletters, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Newsletters, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Newsletters, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Newsletters, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Newsletters, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Newsletters, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Newsletters, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Newsletters, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Newsletters, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Newsletters, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Newsletters, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Newsletters, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Newsletters, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Newsletters, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Membership Directories, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Membership Directories, 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Membership Directories, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Membership Directories, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1981, 1985, and undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Exhibit Rules and Regulations, 1985-2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- General Papers, 1987, 2012, 2014, and undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Fliers, 1984-2016 and undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- The Northern Virginia Postcard Club Newsletters, Book 1, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Northern Virginia Postcard Club Newsletters, Book 2, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The Northern Virginia Postcard Club Newsletters, Book 3, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The Northern Virginia Postcard Club Newsletters, Book 4, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)